Guide to the George Nicolau Papers WAG.250
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Ashforth, et al., Brooklyn College) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Rosalind Barnes) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Board of Higher Education of New York City / Lloyd B. Barzey (Individual Grievant) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Georgia Baumbach) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Steven Berenback Hunter College) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Best, Lehman College) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Professor Irwin Blatt) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Buchen) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Buxbaum) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Cadieu Queens College) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Change of Working Conditions) (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Board of Higher Education of the City of New York / Robert Daniel (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (J. Marion Dickey Queens) (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Downer-Brooklyn College) (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Drucker) (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Fallon) (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Dr. James Fetzer) (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Floeter) (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Jehousa Friedman / Trustees of the City University of New York (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Gamble) (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Gibbs, Montague, and Sellars) (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Grant) (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Greenwald and Swiderski) (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Ralph Green / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Hank) (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - City University of New York / Professional Staff Congress (CUNY) Harris and Jacobs) (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Norman P. Horwitz / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Jansons) (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Janus) (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Jones/ Medgar Evers College) (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Joseph) (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Arlene Mantell Kahn / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Leake) (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Anthony LoSecco / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Leonard) (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Lovell) (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Leifer) (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Macri) (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Macri, II) (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Samuel Margulies / Board of Higher Education (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Martindale) (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Nicholas Mauro / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Mayhew) (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / CUNY (Normore) (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Ndeli and Thaxton) (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Moss) (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Monroe) (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Mendes) (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Mehta) (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Kevin McNulty / Board of Higher Education (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Seidman) (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Ross) (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (A. Rosenthal) (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Charles Romain) (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Richmond) (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Lewis A. Ress / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Reiff) (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Ramjerdi) (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Seymour W. Pustiknik / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Posementier) (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Pasamanick) (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Wimberly) (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Vlahovic) (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Tottossy) (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Toomey) (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Tomlinson) (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Zoltan Tar / Trustees of the City University of New York (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (E. Smith) (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Carole Sirovich / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Simonetti) (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Nathan Waldman / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Ruth Westheimer / Trustees of the City University of New York (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Winer) (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Edward Wolfarth / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Vollmer) (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Voorsanger) (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Wydro) (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - MLB 91-4 (Carlos Diaz) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - MLB 91-1 (Nieves) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - MLBPA (Garvey) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - MLB 91-6, 7, & 8 (Stopemayer, Pitman, & Curry) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - MLB 93-1 (Designated Player) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - NN 84-80N (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - NN 84-100 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - NN 84-163 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - NN 84-164 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - NN 84-201 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - NN 84-202 (Harris) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NN 85-1 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - NN 85-8 & 12 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NN 85-25 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - NN 85-74 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - NN 85-83 (NABET/NBC) (Lee) (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - NN 85-130 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - NN 86-45 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - NN 86-202; 20.10 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - NN 87-1 (NABET/NBC) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Unprocessed Material (Box 17)
  - Unprocessed Material (Box 18)
  - Unprocessed Material (Box 19)
  - Unprocessed Material (Box 20)
  - Unprocessed Material (Box 21)
  - Unprocessed Material (Box 22)
  - 2013 Donation, 1981-2013; 2013.043; 3 boxes
    - Arbitration Awards: Broadcasting, Health Care (Local 1199), Maritime, Communication, Theater, and Transportation, 1981-2013; 2013.043 (Box 23)
    - Arbitration Awards: Airlines, 2002-2013 (Box 24)
    - Arbitration Awards: National Basketball Players Association and Ad Hoc, 1990-2012 (Box 25)